{"test_questions": [[{"question": "What is the applied voltage for a series RLC circuit when IT = 3 mA, VL = 30 V, VC = 18 V, and R = 1000 ohms?", "opta": "3.00 V", "optb": "12.37 V", "optc": "34.98 V", "optd": "48.00 V", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the bandwidth of the circuit?", "opta": "31.8 Hz", "optb": "32.3 Hz", "optc": "142 Hz", "optd": "7.2 kHz", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a parallel RLC circuit, which value may always be used as a vector reference?", "opta": "current", "optb": "reactance", "optc": "resistance", "optd": "voltage", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How much current will flow in a 100 Hz series RLC circuit if VS = 20 V, RT = 66 ohms, and XT = 47 ohms?", "opta": "1.05 A", "optb": "303 mA", "optc": "247 mA", "optd": "107 mA", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the Q (Quality factor) of a series circuit that resonates at 6 kHz, has equal reactance of 4 kilo-ohms each, and a resistor value of 50 ohms?", "opta": "0.001", "optb": "50", "optc": "80", "optd": "4.0", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the range between f1 and f2 of an RLC circuit that resonates at 150 kHz and has a Q of 30?", "opta": "100.0 kHz to 155.0 kHz", "optb": "147.5 kHz to 152.5 kHz", "optc": "4500 kHz to 295.5 kHz", "optd": "149,970 Hz to 150,030 Hz", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the quality factor?", "opta": "999", "optb": "223", "optc": "2.2", "optd": "0.99", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What effect will a parallel tank have upon final filter current?", "opta": "very little", "optb": "The bandpass frequencies will change.", "optc": "The frequency cutoff will change.", "optd": "The impedance will block output.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total current?", "opta": "56.6 mA", "optb": "141 mA", "optc": "191 mA", "optd": "244 mA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When a parallel circuit resonates it is said to:", "opta": "flywheel", "optb": "oscillate", "optc": "both of the above", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the resonant frequency in the given circuit?", "opta": "11.6 Hz", "optb": "275.8 Hz", "optc": "1.5 kHz", "optd": "3.2 kHz", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Series RLC voltage or impedance totals must be calculated by:", "opta": "subtracting the values", "optb": "graphing the angles", "optc": "adding vectors", "optd": "multiplying the values", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total current?", "opta": "15.6 mA", "optb": "17.8 mA", "optc": "21.9 mA", "optd": "26.0 mA", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When XC = XL the circuit:", "opta": "draws maximum current", "optb": "applied voltage is zero", "optc": "is at resonance", "optd": "draws minimum current", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How much current will flow in a series RLC circuit when VT = 100 V, XL = 160 , XC = 80 , and R = 60 ?", "opta": "1 A", "optb": "1 mA", "optc": "6.28 A", "optd": "10 A", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When a full band of frequencies is allowed to pass through a filter circuit to the output, the resonant circuit is called a:", "opta": "low-pass filter", "optb": "high-pass filter", "optc": "band-stop filter", "optd": "bandpass filter", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "At resonance, the term bandwidth includes all frequencies that allow what percentage of maximum current to flow?", "opta": "50", "optb": "62.3", "optc": "70.7", "optd": "95.3", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the voltage across the capacitor in the given circuit?", "opta": "6.8 V", "optb": "11.9 V", "optc": "16.1 V", "optd": "22.9 V", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the impedance of the circuit in the given circuit?", "opta": "1.05 k", "optb": "1.33 k", "optc": "2.19 k", "optd": "3.39 k", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a series RLC circuit the current can be found using:", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "both of the above", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the true power consumed in a 30 V series RLC circuit if Z = 20 ohms and R = 10 ohms?", "opta": "15.0 watts", "optb": "22.5 watts", "optc": "30.0 watts", "optd": "45.0 watts", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the current phase angle for a parallel RLC circuit when IL = 15.3 A, IC = 0.43 A, and IR = 3.5 A?", "opta": "76.7 degrees", "optb": "\u20134.25 degrees", "optc": "88.8 degrees", "optd": "\u201376.7 degrees", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "At any resonant frequency, what voltage is measured across the two series reactive components?", "opta": "applied", "optb": "reactive", "optc": "zero", "optd": "inductive and capacitive", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the resonance frequency?", "opta": "31.8 Hz", "optb": "71 Hz", "optc": "7.1 kHz", "optd": "31.8 kHz", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the range between f1 and f2 of an RLC circuit that resonates at 150 kHz and has a Q of 30?", "opta": "100.0 kHz to 155.0 kHz", "optb": "147.5 kHz to 152.5 kHz", "optc": "4500 kHz to 295.5 kHz", "optd": "149,970 Hz to 150,030 Hz", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the bandwidth in the given circuit. If the winding resistance of the coil is 12 ?", "opta": "6.4 kHz", "optb": "47.2 kHz", "optc": "53.7 kHz", "optd": "60.2 kHz", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "At any resonant frequency, what net voltage is measured across the two series reactive components?", "opta": "Applied voltage", "optb": "Reactive voltage", "optc": "Zero voltage", "optd": "VL + VC voltage", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If the bandwidth of a filter increases:", "opta": "Q decreases", "optb": "the roll-off rate increases", "optc": "the half-power frequency decreases", "optd": "the center frequency decreases", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Series RLC impedance or voltage totals must always be calculated by", "opta": "adding values vectorially", "optb": "graphing the angles", "optc": "multiplying the values", "optd": "subtracting the values", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the current through the capacitor in the given circuit?", "opta": "3.5 mA", "optb": "5.5 mA", "optc": "9 mA", "optd": "11.4 mA", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total impedance of a 60 Hz series RLC circuit when XL = 7.5 ohms, XC = 265.3 ohms, and R = 33 ohms?", "opta": "257.8 ohms", "optb": "259.9 ohms", "optc": "290.8 ohms", "optd": "1989.75 ohms", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the total current for the nonideal circuit in the given circuit. If it is at resonance?", "opta": "0 A", "optb": "284  A", "optc": "3.3 mA", "optd": "38.5 mA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the high cutoff frequency for an RLC circuit that resonates at 2000 Hz and has a bandwidth of 250 Hz?", "opta": "2125 Hz", "optb": "2250 Hz", "optc": "1750 Hz", "optd": "8.0 Hz", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Current in a series RLC circuit may always be used as:", "opta": "a leading vector", "optb": "a reference", "optc": "an angle", "optd": "a lagging vector", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the impedance of the circuit?", "opta": "12.2 k", "optb": "14.5 k", "optc": "17.8 k", "optd": "20.3 k", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the resonant frequency in the given circuit?", "opta": "6.5 kHz", "optb": "53.7 kHz", "optc": "107.4 kHz", "optd": "18.1 MHz", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the impedance of the circuit in the given circuit?", "opta": "125.7", "optb": "297.6", "optc": "370.1", "optd": "423.3", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the approximate phase angle in a series RLC circuit when VC = 117 V, VR = 14.5 V, and VL = 3.3 V?", "opta": "\u201345.0 degrees", "optb": "\u201382.7 degrees", "optc": "\u201390.0 degrees", "optd": "\u2013172.7 degrees", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which statement best describes reactance in a series RLC circuit?", "opta": "Capacitive reactance is always dominant.", "optb": "Inductive reactance is always dominant.", "optc": "Resistance is always dominant.", "optd": "The larger of the two reactances is dominant.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the band pass (F1 \u2013 F2) of an RLC filter that resonates at 150 kHz and has a coil Q of 30?", "opta": "100.0 kHz to 155.0 kHz", "optb": "147.5 kHz to 152.5 kHz", "optc": "295.5 kHz to 4500 kHz", "optd": "149,970 Hz to 150,030 Hz", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the power factor?", "opta": "0.279", "optb": "0.479", "optc": "0.679", "optd": "0.879", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the phase angle?", "opta": "61.4\u00ba", "optb": "28.5\u00ba", "optc": "-28.5\u00ba", "optd": "-61.4\u00ba", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What would be the power factor for an RLC circuit that acts inductively?", "opta": "+90 degrees leading", "optb": "one", "optc": "zero", "optd": "\u201390 degrees lagging", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Voltage lags current in an RLC circuit when it acts:", "opta": "capacitively", "optb": "resistively", "optc": "inductively", "optd": "resonantly", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the bandwidth of the circuit in the given circuit?", "opta": "11.6 Hz", "optb": "275.9 Hz", "optc": "1.5 kHz", "optd": "3.2 kHz", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the voltage across R1, C1, and L1?", "opta": "VR = 156 V, VC = 165 V, VL = 441 V", "optb": "VR = 178 V, VC = 187 V, VL = 503 V", "optc": "VR = 219 V, VC = 232 V, VL = 619 V", "optd": "VR = 260 V, VC = 276 V, VL = 735 V", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}